{
    "subject": "resource/Alfonso,_Prince_of_Asturias_(1907\u20131938)",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Spain",
    "human_readable": "Alfonso, Prince of Asturias (1907\u20131938) was born in Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9867323040962219,
            "question": "Was Alfonso, Prince of Asturias born in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9432211518287659,
            "question": "Where was Alfonso, Prince of Asturias born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9228091239929199,
            "question": "Who was Alfonso, Prince of Asturias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8220338225364685,
            "question": "What was Alfonso, Prince of Asturias' title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7924270033836365,
            "question": "Can you provide information about Alfonso, Prince of Asturias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7710919976234436,
            "question": "What country was associated with Alfonso, Prince of Asturias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7397468686103821,
            "question": "What years did Alfonso, Prince of Asturias live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7338417172431946,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Alfonso, Prince of Asturias' family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7197638154029846,
            "question": "When did Alfonso, Prince of Asturias die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7139438390731812,
            "question": "What is known about the life of Alfonso, Prince of Asturias?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alfonso, Prince of Asturias (1907\u20131938) was born in Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3205_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Alfonso, Prince of Asturias die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3205_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Alfonso, Prince of Asturias' family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3205_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What years did Alfonso, Prince of Asturias live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3205_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3205_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Alfonso, Prince of Asturias was born on May 10, 1907, in Madrid, Spain. Therefore, the statement that he was born in Spain is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}